Guide to the Mon Valley Unemployed Committee Collection, 1973-1998 AIS.2002.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Newsletters and Media, 1982-1991; IV.
  - MVUC Benefit Pamphlet, July 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - MVUC Newsletter, August 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Labor Notes", August 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - MVUC Newsletter, August 1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - October 6th Rally Information, September 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - MVUC Newsletter, December 8, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Central Labor Union-Senator Heinz, December 20, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - MVUC "Mortgage Project Pays Off", undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "Reagan Says Cutback-We Say Fight back", undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Good News, Bad News", undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Now You Can Get A Little Help", undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "State Support for the October 6th Rally", undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "American Dream Turns Nightmare", undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - MVU Media Coverage, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Media History, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Media Coverage, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - NUN News, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - "Unemployment Grows, A New Movement Stirs", 1983 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Jobless Action Units", January 1983 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - NUN Newsletter, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - NUN Newsletter, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - MVUC Information Sheet, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - History of MVUC, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - "Labor Notes", 1983 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - MVUC "Eat Cheese" Newsletter, April 1983 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - MVUC Newsletter, May 1983-December 1983 (Box 16, Folder 35-39)
  - Press Statement, December 1983 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Utilities Campaign, Press Releases and News clippings, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 41-53)
  - Mortgage Campaign, Press Releases and News clippings, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 54-71)
  - Health Care Information, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 72-73)
  - Public Relations for Unemployed Hotline, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Press Releases for Unemployed Hotline, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Legislation Committee Meetings Flyer, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - NUN News clippings, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - MVUC Publicity, Newsletters, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "The Mon Valley Struggles to Find Life after Steel", May 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - MVUC Newsletter, Spring 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - NUN Notes, June 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - MVUC "Duquesne Slated for Destruction", July 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - MVUC Newsletter, August 1984-November 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
  - "The New People", November 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - MVUC News, December 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "Movement Grows to Keep Steel in Valley", December 1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Economic Dislocation", undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - St. Peters/Mon Valley Food Program, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - MVUC Pamphlets, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "Health Committee Hotline", undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - "Fuel Program" Information, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - MVUC Propaganda, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "Unemployment March for Survival", undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - MVUC Newsletters, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "Keep Federal Unemployment Benefits", January 1985 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - MVUC Newsletter, February 1985-October 1985 (Box 17, Folder 23-29)
  - "Save Your Home from Foreclosures", undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - MVUC Policy Council Newsletter, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - "Help Us, Help You", undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Allegheny Conference's Pittsburgh Program for Affordable Health Care, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 33-34)
  - MVUC Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 35-38)
  - Steel Crisis News Clippings, April 1986 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - "Shortchanged", February 1987 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - TAA/TRA Campaign Update, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Washington Post Articles on MVUC, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - MVUC Newsletters, May-June 1988 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Publications and News Releases, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - "We Need Your Support Again", August 1988 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - MVUC TAA/TRA Campaign Update, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - MVUC Year End Report, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - MVUC Newsletters, January 1986-April 1988 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - News Clippings MVUC, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Welfare Lien Campaign Media for October Lobby, October 3, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - News Clippings about MVUC, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - News clippings, press releases and publications, microfilm, 1980, 1982-1984 (Microfilm-cabinet 3, Drawer 7, Reel 1)
- Unemployment Conference Materials, 1979-1986; V.
  This series contains records of conferences the MVUC attended and participated in from 1981 to 1986. Most of the files pertain to the MVUC's participation in the Tri-State Conference of Steel from 1981 to 1983, the Comeback Conference of 1984, which includes a set of photographic slides, and the National Unemployment Conference of 1984. This series also contains documents on effective leadership and organizing strategies. This series is arranges by conference.
  - Comeback Conference Slides, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Series of Papers on Community Regeneration by Presley, Rodale, Regen, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Information about Local Initiatives Support Corp., 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Paper "The Rhode Island Strategic Development Commission: Labor's Perspective," By Edward McElroy, Jr. and Tracy Fitzpatrick, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Book, "Economic Dislocation: Plant Closings, Relocation and Conversion", 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Tri-State Conference on Steel "Steel Valley Authority: A Community Plan to Save Pittsburgh's Steel Industry (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Job Creation, undated (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - NUN Conference Material, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Comeback Conference, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9-15)
  - Small Issue Industrial Revenue Bonds for Job Creation, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Paul Lodico's NUN 1984 Conference Notes (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Book, "A Working Economy" By Bob Kuttner, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Comeback Conference Flyers, May 4-5, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
  - List of Workshops at Comeback Conference, May 4-5, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 3 Rivers Economic Development Coalition, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - MVUC Comeback Conference, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - PP&P Co. Armour Workers Unites, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Mesta Buyout, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Labor, Comeback Conference, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Workshop Handouts NUN Conference, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - NUN Conference, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 28-35)
  - 3 Rivers of Progress Symposium, September 27-28, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Tri-State Steel, Fall 1984-Spring 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Unemployed People's Hearing, March 8, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Employee Assistance Center- Roskowski, Fall 1984-Winter 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - $190 Million Bond for Economic Development, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - McKeesport Job Development, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Save Dorothy 6 and Tri-State Coalition, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Tri-State Conference on Steel, October 23, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 9-13)
  - Employed Registration Form: Comeback Conference, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)